ceibs.edu 2018-05-12

# Privacy Policy | CEIBS

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [www.ceibs.edu](http://www.ceibs.edu/). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by notifying the party with which you have made initial contact, contacting us via [webmaster@ceibs.edu](mailto:webmaster@ceibs.edu) or by calling +86-21-2890 5890.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Updates**  
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately by phone at +86-21-2890 5890 or by emailing us at**[webmaster@ceibs.edu](mailto:webmaster@ceibs.edu) **.**
